本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 阿休休 易如反掌 Mstower 白云喵喵
校对&后期： 阿休休
妖女迷行 第三季第三集
坎耶・欧马立・韦斯特 美国说唱歌手
星球大战反派 天行者阿纳金黑化后改名为达斯・维达
双关：勃起
温迪・怀内嘉宾
有些人就是没法接受"不行"这个回答
Some guys just can't take "No" For an answer.
莫瑞根命令要回那张照片!
The Morrigan wants that photo!
哦 这事我还真不能怪她 你看了没?
Oh, I can't blame her. Have you seen it?
不太雅观啊!
Awkward!
肯吉助攻!得分!
Kenzi for the assist! Yes!
你觉得那招如何? 我假装摔倒
Did you like that part? Where I pretended to fall on my ass
但其实像颗隐形导弹一样正中目标
when actually I was like a stealth missile lasering in on target.
干得好 记得提醒我帮你报名"与异种共舞"
Smooth. Remind me to book you on "Dancing With The Fae".
有那种玩意儿?
Is that a thing?
少说话多做事 快帮我把这高丑黑拽走 好吗?
Just help me drag tall, dark and hideous out of sight, okay?
你懂得 要成为温迪・怀内我还欠火候
You know, far be it from me to be a Wendy Whiner...
毫无悬念
Totally.
但这是本周第三次混球异种来袭了
But this is the third Faebag attack this week.
你什么意思 温迪?
Your point, Wendy?
昨天是一个长的像里吉斯的双头怪
Yesterday it was the two-headed thingie that looked like Regis.
那之前是个卖热狗的小贩
Then before that it was that hotdog vendor
但其实是个喷火的...?
that turned out to be a fire- breathing...?
- 要我说应该是 青蛙? - 海蜇?
- I wanna say, frog? - Jellyfish?
管它是什么 我们海扁了它一顿
Whatever it was, we kicked its gelatinous ass.
我从未想过我会这么说 但我就是个人类 波
You know, I never thought I'd say this, but I'm only human, Bo.
无意冒犯 遇上这事你也不怎么欢乐啊
And, no offense, but you ain't lookin' so chipper either.
无论莫瑞根派来什么异种 我都应付得了
Hey, whatever the Morrigan dishes out, I can handle it.
昨天那记铁拳打得你还头晕否?
You still got that doozie from yesterday's slug fest?
昨天那是刀伤
Yesterday it was a cut.
今天是淤青 我在愈合中
Today it is a bruise. I'm healing.
- 慢慢地 要很慢地 - 你说什么呢?
- Slowly. Very slowly. - What are you saying?
那个医生...我意思是...
The doc... I mean...
像不像是用仓鼠滚轮
you know, isn't it like trying to charge an iPad
- 试着给Ipad充电? - 好吧 暂停一下
- with a hamster wheel? - Okay, time out.
你到底哪儿不待见劳伦?
What exactly do you have against Lauren?
啥?
Moi?
得了 肯吉
Oh, come on, Kenzi, with
你那些个挖苦加翻白眼
the little digs and the rolling of the eyes...
- 我又不傻 - 呃...
- I'm not stupid. - Well...
这可是机会 趁我还撑得住
Here's your chance, while I'm still high
不想吸元疗伤之时 发泄出来吧
off my wicked moves. Get it out of your system!
她爱指手画脚 占有欲强 控制欲强
She is bossy, territorial, and controlling.
她觉得你幼稚 不负责任 还粘人
She thinks you're immature, irresponsible and clingy.
你这么说!?
She does!?
你自己都那么说过自己
Oh, you've said those things about yourself.
是啊 但是自己说自己那叫可爱好吗
Yeah, but when I say it, it is adorable.
好吧 关键是我爱劳伦
Okay, the point is I love Lauren.
她对我很重要 你也是
She's a huge part of my life. As are you.
所以这场"闺蜜"对战"女友"的戏码
So in the Battle of BFF versus Main Squeeze,
我们该叫停了 明白吗?
I think it's time we called a truce. Got it?
现在 大家和波一条心 去喝酒吧 我请客
Now, all those on Team Bo... drinks are on me.
那才对...
That's right...
布鲁斯...你真让我失望
Oh, Bruce... you disappoint me.
- 我叫斯蒂夫 - 怎么回事呢?
- I'm Steve... - How did this happen?
不是我的错 她有个后援
It's not my fault, she had an army.
- 别侮辱我的智商!
- Don't insult my intelligence!
你撒谎功力比你哥哥埃里克都差
You're a worse liar than your brother, Eric.
- 他叫戴夫 - 我才不管!
- Dave. - I don't care!
要不是我刚去做了美甲
If I hadn't just had my nails done,
我早就亲手把你的心挖出来了
I'd rip your beating heart out myself.
您真是太善良了
You're too kind.
我觉得某人的气焰
I think someone's getting
真是越来越嚣张了
a little too big for her leather britches.
快了 我的乖乖...快了
Soon, my pet... soon.
如果我们的小淫妖觉得玩得起
If Li'l Bo Bleep thinks she can play in the big leagues...
那就让游戏开始吧
let the games begin.
当你不知道你是谁时 生活会很艰辛
Life is hard when you don't know who you are.
当你知道真相后 生活会更艰难
It's harder when you don't know what you are.
我的爱伴随死神的降临
My love carries a death sentence.
我迷失了多年 在藏匿中找寻
I was lost for years, searching while hiding.
那个不为人知的属于我的世界
Only to find that I belonged to a world hidden from humans.
但我已经厌倦了躲藏
I won't hide anymore.
我要过自己想要的生活
I will live the life I choose.
心电图 核磁共振 植物病毒检查
Ekg, mri, emv...
读到虐恋剧情的时候再叫我
Wake me up when you get to S&M.
看吧 事实上 伐克斯...
See, the truth of it, Vex, is that...
别 别忽悠我 医生 有话直说吧
No, don't sugar coat it, Doc. Just give it to me straight.
好吧 生理学上看 你的胳膊已经痊愈了
Okay... there is nothing physically wrong with your arm,
而且神经系统 肌肉骨系统也没什么问题...
or your nervous system, or your musculoskeletal system...
那 为什么 我不能
Then... why... can't I...
- 使用异种能力? - 你还真会定期爆点
- Get it up? - Oh, regular riot, you are.
既然没有生理学上的理论
Since there's no physiological
来解释你的催眠术为什么无效
reason for your mesmeric impotence...
啊哈!我让你挠痒痒了!
Aha! I made you do that!
- 没 其实 刚刚只是有点痒 - 该死的!
- No, actually, that was just an itch. - Damn you!
我意思是你的"情况"
What I'm trying to say is that your "Condition"
可能实际是心理问题
may be psychological in nature.
你意思是我废了?
What, you sayin' I'm whacked?
像个疯子似的? 傻子缺八两?
Like I'm a nutter? A few ounces short of a pound?
以你的年纪 这现象很常见
It's not at all uncommon in Fae your age.
你知道你在跟谁说话吗?
Do you have any idea who you're talking to?
让你感受一下伐克斯之怒!
You shall feel the wrath of Vex!
擦
Bah!
你怎么还没勒死自己?!
Why aren't you strangling yourself by now?!
没什么好尴尬的
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
其实我有本小册子...
I actually have the pamphlet...
哦 省省你那套可悲的医生对病人态度
Oh, save your pathetic bedside manner
留给你那不长久的新女友吧
for your new, presumably temporary, girlfriend!
- 什么? - 哦 得了...要满足
- Excuse me? - Oh, come on... it can't be easy
上发条的淫妖兔的欲望可不容易啊
keepin' up with the Energizer SuccuBunny.
虽然戴森可以
Though Dyson could.
好吧 我觉得我们完事了
Okay... you know what? I think we're done.
不给我换点药吗
Any chance of a prescription refill?
- 出去! - 真的吗?
- Out! - Really?
无情的医生
Bloody physicians.
想象一下 假设什么也没问题
I mean, imagine sayin' that there's nothing wrong with it.
你听过这么扯的
I mean, have you ever heard anything so...
喂! 酒保! 我在跟你说话!
Hello! Barkeep! I'm talking to you!
- 还在说? - 难以置信!
- Still? - Unbelievable!
我在这儿掏心挖肺 你却
Here I am, pouring out my heart to you and...
好吧 戴森 我可不是来娱乐的
Ok Dyson, I'm not here for my health.
你到底看不看这些文件?
You wanna look at these case files or not?
肯定看 再等等
Uh, absolutely. Just gimme a sec...
啊...问候你们呀
Ah... greetings.
- 闭嘴 伐克斯 - 什么?
- Don't even start, Vex. - I beg your pardon?
- 我不会再给你买酒了 - 嘿  我很受伤诶
- I'm not buying you another drink. - Hey, I'm deeply offended.
- 很好 现在滚吧 - 嘿 你管不着我
- Good, now go away. - Hey, you don't own me.
好吧 听着...
Okay, look...
你那悲惨遭遇我们已经听得耳朵起茧了
we've been listening to your same sad story for days.
黑暗异族不想要我 光明异族受不了我
The Dark doesn't want me. The Light can't stand me.
我的朋友们...哦等等...
My friends... Oh, wait...
他没有朋友 是吧?
he doesn't have any, does he?
- 伐克斯弱爆了 - 这是在侮辱我!
- Sucks to be Vex. - This is an outrage!
九号球 横袋
Nine ball... side pocket.
那个妞怎么回事?
What is it with that chick?
她不待见你而已
She's just not feeling the love.
- 但为什么? -因为她觉得你是个杀人犯?
- But why? - Because she thinks you're a murderer?
但更重要的是 你最近在忙什么?
But more importantly, what have you been up to?
什么? 哦...
What? Oh...
- 又是莫瑞根? - 哦 小菜一碟
- The Morrigan again? - Oh, piece of cake.
别小看那个女人
Don't underestimate that woman.
迦楼罗被打败之后 光明异族
After the Garuda meltdown, the Light
和黑暗异族决定握手言和
and the Dark have agreed to play nice.
不结盟表示无保护
Unaligned means unprotected.
但是你忘了...
Oh, but you are forgetting...
我有这个
I have this.
我自己的小小保险
My own little insurance policy.
我还是觉得你应该跟阿什谈一下
I still think you should talk to The Ash.
你看起来得好好休息一整子
You look like you could use a break.
我猜肯吉也可以
And I'm guessing Kenzi could, too.
不好意思...
Pardonez moi...
- 他又怎么了? - 我不知道
- What's his problem? - I have no idea.
你自找的 你懂得
You brought this on yourself, you know.
你就是这么当阿什的? 严爱政策?
Is this how you roll now? Tough love?
是你把莫瑞根拷在床上 拍了她的不雅照
You handcuffed the Morrigan to her bed for a Kodak moment.
你确定这跟
You sure this has nothing
你的异种联合国实验没关系?
to do with your Fae United Nations experiment?
光明异种和黑暗异种搭档办案? 搞毛?
A Light cop partnered with a Dark cop? Really?
正是这种愤世嫉俗
It's cynicism like that has kept our sides
阻碍了真正和平的建立
from building a genuine peace.
还有 你戴森跟谁搞在一起管你什么事?
Also, why do you care who Dyson is paired with?
- 我没有 - 我可不觉得
- I don't. - Didn't think so.
知道怎么做可以帮你摆脱现状吗?
Know what might help your situation?
碰巧我准备好了对光明异族的宣言书
Just so happens I had a declaration to the Light all prepared...
我是不会因为恐惧而被迫选择阵营的
I'm not gonna be pressured into choosing a side out of fear.
好吧 不能怪我想试试
Well, can't blame an Ash for tryin'.
听着 别管我了 我自己能解决这堆麻烦
You know what? Forget it. I can handle the shitstorm,
只是肯吉自己在纠结而已
it's just that Kenzi is starting to feel the strain.
现在谁才在上演严爱戏码?
Now who's dishing out tough love?
波 等一下...
Bo, hang on...
听着 自从我们解决掉迦楼罗之后
Look, since we got all Garuda-fied,
我一直在整理保存的机密文档
I've been doing some serious inventory of the archives.
结果?
And... ?
似乎有人偷走了我的正义之杖
Seems someone has grabbed my Staff of Righteousness.
是一根木制的权杖
The Staff is a piece of wood...
珍贵的仪式遗物...能力强大
a treasured ceremonial relic ... and very powerful.
据调查这权杖最近现在
Currently believed to be in the possession
在莫蒂默・法斯宾德的手上 卑鄙的典当商
of one Mortimer Fassbinder. Pawnbroker and sleazebag.
所以 如果我把权杖带来给你...
So, if I bring you this Staff...
我也许会派一支特遣队到你家附近
I could probably post a security detail near your place.
帮你留意莫瑞根的宠物
Keep an eye out for The Morrigan's pets.
- 我去哪里找这个法斯宾德? - 别心急 看反面
- Where do I find this Fassbinder? - Hold up, Slick...
你必须了解一下这权杖的背景知识
There's something you should know about the Staff.
谢了 布鲁斯!
Cheers, Bruce!
可爱的女士 今天是你的幸运日
Lovely lady, it is your lucky day.
你迈入门槛那刻我就可以杀了
I could have you killed just for crossing my threshold.
啧啧 冤冤相报何时了
Tut tut, bygones and all that...
请让我深切表达我对黑暗异族和你的忠诚
A heartfelt expression of my loyalty to the Dark. And you.
被困的我依然勾人
I am beautiful in restraints.
删除...
Delete...
- 还有什么别的事吗? - 哦 你不该高兴才对吗
- Was there something else? - Well, I thought you'd be pleased.
如果你真心想讨好我
If you really wanted to please me you would have
你就该提着那小贱人的头来见我
brought me that bitch's head on a platter.
但是... 但是我...
But... but, I...
但是最近你好像异种能力尽失?
But maybe your recent bout of impotence has spread to your spine?
算你走运 我同情心泛滥
Lucky for you, my pity outweighs my disgust.
我不会杀掉你的 至少不是今天
I won't have you killed. At least not today.
哦... 你太大度了
Oh... you're too kind.
我们都有自己的苦衷
We all have our cross to bear.
喝了它快滚吧
Now drink up and go.
下次我见到你...
The next time we meet...
你和波不是她死就是你亡 你自己选择吧
...either Bo or you will be dead. The choice is yours.
- 嗨 - 哦 嗨
- Hey. - Oh, hey.
你在做什么?
Whatcha doin'?
哦 只是做些医生的实验
Oh, you know, just some Doctor-y stuff.
你知道 我确实对你的工作很感兴趣
You know, I am actually interested in your work.
你可以告诉我你在做什么的
You can talk to me about whatever it is you do.
真的? 你想听听我最近着手的论文
Really? You want to hear about my latest monograph
关于与人类血液相比异种血液的
regarding the rhizome repellent gradient of Fae blood compared
排斥梯度
with human blood,
尤其是当其悬浮在等渗溶液中
especially when suspended in an isotonic solution?
- 或者我们可以去看部电影 - 好吧
- Or we could go to a movie. - Okay.
- 那是什么? - 哦...
- What is that? - Oh...
- 正义之杖 - 什么玩意?
- The Staff of Righteousness. - The who of what?
别问了 哦 也别碰
Don't ask. Oh, and don't touch.
那么 我能摸什么?
Well... what can I touch?
啊哈 真有趣
Haha, very funny.
你怎么啦?
What's gotten into you?
怎么说 本来还真没啥目的
Well, you know, nothing just yet.
但是现在我想也许我们可以...
But I was kinda thinking maybe we could, um...
哦...
Oh...
哇 我以为我只是顺路经过
wow... I think I just came by
看看我的手机是不是落在这里
to see if I left my phone here.
嗯... 我不清楚 让我们看看...
Hmm... I don't know. Let's look...
它不在这里 天啊
Well, it's not in there. Gosh, you know,
也许你把它调到震动模式了
with any luck maybe you left it on "Vibrate".
我以为昨晚之后你会很疲倦
I thought you'd be too tired after last night.
疲倦? 我可是力争金牌啊
Tired? I am going for the gold in the Succu-games.
好吧... 我不知道你怎么了
Well... I don't know what's gotten into you,
但我不能阻碍
but far be it from me to
一个年轻运动员的夺金梦
stand in the way of a young athlete's dream.
- 呦 阿伐 - 随你怎么叫
- Yo, V-man. - Whatever.
听上去好像某人情绪低落啊
Sounds like somebody woke up on the wrong side
换了个人似的 怎么啦?
of the pull-out couch this morning. What's up?
- 是我的胳膊 - 又在讨同情了?
- It's my arm. - Again with the pity parade?
听着 你的翅膀折了 你不能飞了
Look, you got a busted wing, you can't fly.
你要像我们这些可悲的人类一样活着了
You gotta walk around like the rest of us poor miserable humans.
欢迎来到肯吉的世界! 老兄!
Welcome to Kenzi-ville! Man!
现在你知道每天被一群超级英雄
Now you know what it's like to be surrounded
环绕左右的感觉了吧 别抱怨了 可怜虫
by superheroes every day. Suck it up, Pathetico!
如果我是你 我会重新考虑在做社工
You know, if I were you, I'd re-consider a career in social work.
我们能不能
Can we just...
忽略你的异种身份哪怕十亿分之一秒
...forget about your Fae-self for like a nanosecond,
来聊一聊真正重要的事情?
and talk about something that's really important?
我表示怀疑
Doubtful.
- 睫毛膏 - 我洗耳恭听
- Mascara. - You have my attention.
老兄 你的睫毛美翻了!
Dude, your lashes are freakin' amazing!
是啊...刷睫毛的手法最重要 等等
Yeah... it's all in the brush technique. Wait...
我在达・芬奇那里找到了些小窍门
I picked up a few tips from Da Vinci.
- 像达芬奇密码一样? - 对 现在那里有个娘炮
- As in The Code? - Oh, yeah, now there was a queen for ya.
他就是戴维的跟屁虫
He was all over David's ass like curry on chips.
- 你能帮我整理下结块的睫毛吗? - 哦别这样
- Can you help me with my clumping? - Oh, please...
嗨 大家伙
Hey, y'all.
嗨... 怎么了?
Hey... Whazat?
长话短说 这就是个关于
The end of a long story, involving
谄媚的典当商和暧昧谈判的故事
a greasy pawnbroker and some hardcore negotiating.
呃 别吵 我们在做正事呢
Uh, do you mind? We're working over here.
有人看见我的手机了吗?
Anyone seen my phone?
你说手机? 怎么 你的手机?
You say phone? What, your phone?
听着 高抬贵臀让我看看坐垫下面有没有
Here, shift a cheek so I can look under the cushions...
没有
Nothing...
- 往旁边挪! - 你最后一次用它在哪里?
- Scootch! - Where'd you last have it?
这就是问题关键... 我发誓我把它放在...
That's the thing... I coulda sworn that I left it...
Ipad Iphone什么的电子产品
Yeah, iPads, iPhones electricity...
说实话 只是一时狂热而已
it's all just a fad, really.
类似产品数不胜数 真理哦
The future's analog and all that. I'm tellin' ya.
我这么刷对吗?
Am I doing it right?
呃...
Uh...
嗯... 再往上一点...
Hmm... just a little bit up...
我 的 天
O.M.G.
你们在一起太有爱了
You guys are so cute together.
- 哈! - 呵...
- Ha! - Huh...
但愿我也能有个一起化妆的伙伴
I wish I had a makeup buddy.
我本以为她可以成为朋友 可她压根就不喜欢我
I thought she could be my friend, and she doesn't even like me.
- 谁? - 塔米辛!
- Who? - Tamsin!
她老刻薄了 对吧?
She is so mean girl, right?
我的意思是 就一个拥有实际人格的异种来说
I mean, buy an actual personality already.
你该不会是碰巧搜了我的行李箱
Did you happen to rifle through my duffel bag,
然后吞掉了那些老虎图案的黄色药片?
and scarf down a couple of yellow pills with tigers on 'em?
我要跟戴森谈谈
I'm gonna talk to Dyson.
顺便说一下 这可以是私人秘密
and BTW?, It is "trés" private.
私密?
Private?
劳伦要怒火中烧了!
Lauren's pelt is gonna be steamed!
你跟那个医生又是什么恩怨?
What's it with you and the Doc?
我指 除了她对病人的态度
I mean, besides her terrible bedside manner
和她脑瓜比你灵的事实
and the fact that she's a damn sight cleverer than you.
还很卑鄙 她在监视波
Not to mention sneaky. She spy-banged Bo.
可戴森伤了波这么多次
Dyson's drop-kicked Bo's heart ten times over,
而且他在的时候你还对他大吼大叫的
and you still howl when he comes 'round.
我...! 没有!
I...! No!
听着 你到底还要不要教我
Listen, are you gonna teach me
双面防水防污刷睫毛法了?
the double pump smudge-proof technique or not?
我为你感到骄傲 过来...
I'm so proud of you. Come here...
好了 你要像这样刷睫毛根部
Alright, you're gonna move it like this just at the ends.
你不要... 手抖...
You can't... like shake it...
我不喜欢你朋友
I do not like your friend.
她不是我朋友 她只是我的新搭档
She's not my friend. She is my new partner.
她怎么说的我?
What is she saying about me?
不管她怎么说 那都不是真的
Because whatever it is, it's not true.
- 你喝高了? - 什么? 你指酒?
- Have you been drinking? - What? Like, alcohol?
我倒希望如此
I wish.
- 你有假身份证吗? - 什么?
- Do you have fake ID? - What?
我们做吧
Let's do it.
我们去吧
Let's get faced!
好吧 你有点不对劲 我要去跟特里克谈谈
Okay, you are cut off. I'm gonna talk to Trick.
哇 你真美
Wow, you're so beautiful.
抱歉...
I'm sorry...
我得走了...
I gotta go...
- 我认为戴森喜欢我 - 什么?
- I think Dyson likes me. - Say what?
别告诉别人... 但我有吻他的冲动!
Don't tell anyone this... but I think I might kiss him!
瞳孔没有扩张...
There's no pupil dilation...
没有脑震荡
no concussion...
我困惑了
I'm stumped.
你的眼眸就像星星一样闪亮
You have little specks in your eyes that look like stars.
当我多虑了 但是你
Call me crazy, but based on
在酒吧的状态
your little display at the bar...
我是说 我知道你和戴森有过去
I mean, I do know that you and Dyson...
三号通道泄露! 三号通道泄露!
Spill on aisle 3! Spill on aisle 3!
嗷 嗷
Ow, ow...
来嘛! 我们去看电影吧
Come on! Let's go to a movie.
哇 火辣的美妞 你吻过女孩不?
Wow, you're really hot. Have you ever kissed a girl?
我需要你乖乖坐好 还得检查你的心电图 好吗?
I need you to sit still to check your EKG, ok?
- 呲 - 波 别闹!
- Bzzz! - Bo, stop!
现在我们已经交换了脑电波
We have now swapped brains.
嗨 我是劳伦医生 我特无趣
Hi, I'm Dr. Lauren. I don't like to have any fun.
带两个皱眉图案的布朗尼蛋糕 明天打电话找我吧
Take two frownie brownies and call me in the morning.
你这样儿真吓到我了
You're really starting to scare me.
好了 波 听我说
Okay Bo... just listen to me...
波! 听我说
Bo! Listen to me...
你最近有接触过陌生的异种吗
have you come in contact with any strange Fae lately...?
- 这太无聊了 - 波 拜托!
- This is so lame! - Bo! Please!
好吧
Okay, well...
倒是遇到一个挥着魔棒的恶男
there was this one gross guy with a magic stick...
嗨 塔米儿 塔辛 砰砰辛警官
Hey, Tammers. "T-sin". Officer "Slamsin"!
- 好吧 - 你这是在自娱自乐吗?
- Okay... - Are you playin' with yourself?
这是谁拿啤酒把你给灌倒了?
Did somebody spike your brewski?
兄弟 这一刻终于发生了
Dude... this one time That totally happened.
我要扮肯吉 一个模子刻出来的有木有
I got to be Kenzi. Nailed it.
好吧 这要是是你想在我们办案前就想让我出局
Right... if you're trying to throw me off my game
这招还真管用了
before we get down, it's working.
- 你觉得波对我有好感吗? - 我看着像管这种闲事的人么
- Do you think Bo likes me? - Do I look like I care?
我想约她出去
I think I'm gonna ask her on a date.
好吧 你自便吧
Okay, well... knock yourself out.
于此同时 你要不就一起玩
In the meantime... you're either in the game...
- 要不就别挡道 - 你真是个坏家伙
- or you are in my way... - You are so badass.
波和戴森排排坐树上
Bo and Dyson sitting in a tree...!
嘘!
Shhhhhh!
亲亲吻吻真亲密
K-I-s-s-I-n-g!
哦 这场景太浪漫了! 但是 嘘! 隔墙有耳
Oh, that would be so awesome! But, shhh! People are listening.
- 嗨 爷爷 这是啥? - 十七世纪
- Hey, Gramps, what's this? - Seventh century.
拜托 请把它放回我的书桌
Please, put it back in my study.
- 恶 她样子好丑 - 把它放回去
- Ew, she's gross. - Just put it back.
把它放回去 能把车钥匙给我吗?
"Put it back." Can I have the car keys?
不行
No.
要是不给我车钥匙 我就用法语数数
If I don't get the car keys, I'm gonna count to a hundred.
数到一百为止
In French .
- 老天 - 看到没?
- Good grief... - See what I mean?
一
Un.
二!
Deux!
三
Trois...
你觉得她这症状
You think this is being
像是因为阿什派她处理的任务而引起的吗?
caused by the job that The Ash sent her on?
四
Quatre...
你说呢
You tell me.
四
Quatre...
会不会是正义之杖引起这样的症状?
Can the Staff of Righteousness have symptoms like these?
- 四! - 是五!
- Quatre...! - Cinq!
- 我的神 是五! - 抱歉 法国警官
- For the love of Aphrodite, it's cinq! - Sorry, French Police.
五
Cinq.
六
Six...
乍看之下 没有记录
At first glance, there's nothing in the lore
显示这根权杖会引起这样的症状
that suggest the Staff is causing her symptoms.
但你也不能否认 这是很诡异的巧合
You have to admit, it's a pretty strange coincidence.
她找回权杖后 就成现在这个
She goes looking for the Staff and comes back like...
- 无忧无虑的傻妞 - 没错
- Pollyanna on mushrooms? - Exactly.
- 嗨 - 怎么了?
- Hey... - What?
怎么没听到数七?
Where's "Seven"?
波 快下来!
Bo, get down!
嘿! 让我跳完! 别对我说教
Hey! Let me finish! Don't Kanye me.
- 你作弊! - 你能奈我何!
- You are a cheater! - Whatever!
你个骗子 诅咒你长痘痘
You're a cheater. And you're getting a zit.
波说的对 你个刻薄的女人!
Bo is right. You're mean!
不管是什么引起的 这症状会传染
Whatever this is... it's contagious.
别用棕色了 黑色才能刷出新意
...you gotta forget about brown... black is always the new black.
- 你别老跟着我们 - 是啊 你又不是我们的老妈
- You can't ground us. - Yeah. You're not our Mom.
没错 我们才不要听你的话
Yeah, we don't even have to listen to you.
所以 波把他俩都带疯了?
So... Bo shagged them both daft?
- 我们有麻烦了 - 更像是烂麻烦
- We have a situation. - More like a SHITuation.
你们像参观参观我的卧室吗?
You guys wanna see my room?
- 额 当然 - 看谁跑得快!
- Uh... yeah! - Shotgun!
- 不! 不! - 别 等等! 等等!
- No! No! - No, wait! Wait!
有东西引起了这个症状 更糟糕的是
Something's made them sick. And what's worse is the...
- 这是? - 一头猪?
- Is that...? - A pig...?
他在寻找些什么东西
He's looking for something...
或是什么人! 波
Or someone! Bo...
肯吉 刀在哪儿? 你的工具箱也行?
Kenzi, where is there a knife? Or your trunk?
- 额 在楼上呢! - 好吧 那你的剑呢?
- Uh, upstairs! - Well, what about your sword??
- 在 楼上! - 好吧 肯吉 赶紧想办法!
- Up... stairs! - Okay, well, Kenzi, think of something!
动脑筋神马的不是一般都是你的事么 医生!
That's usually your thing, Doc!
这只小肥猪就准备去市场挂售吧
This little piggy's about to go to market!
我们需要武器! 我们需要东西来防卫!
We need a weapon! We need something!
该死的
Bloody hell...
行了 猪猪 行了
That'll do, pig... that'll do.
你是怎么
How did you...
我
I...
原来你才是匹黑马
Aren't you the dark horse.
他死了
He's dead.
兄弟 我只是随手抓了根棍子
Dudes, all I did was grab this stupid shillelagh
然后突然之间我就成了达斯・维达
and all of a sudden I'm Darth Vader.
- 让我看看 - 说起这个
- Let me see that... - Yeah, about that...
这棍子貌似有点 粘在手上拿不下来了
the shaft is kinda... Fae-zy Glued to my hand.
是啊 我也有类似经历
Yeah... That happened to me once.
苦不堪言
Painful.
"赶紧拿个武器"她如是说
"Grab a weapon," She said.
这看起来像是高能键
It seems to be an energy bond.
- 那就解开键连呐 - 做不到啊
- So un-bond it. - I can't.
这木头和你手上的肉融为一体了
The wood is melded to your flesh.
世上最挫的手淫工具
Worst hand job ever.
哇 老兄! 拿刀作甚?
Whoa, Mack! The knife!?
不是啊 我电视上看到的 切木头和番茄
No, I saw it on TV. It cuts right through wood.
轻而易举
And tomatoes.
不是我的错 棍子惹的祸
Not my bad. Stick bad.
还有 这音乐难听死了!
Plus... your music sucks!
我买那碟是用来鄙视的
I bought that one ironically.
说实话 没看得上眼的
All of them, actually...
- 额 这到底是啥? - 哦 看看这货!
- Um, what the heck is this? - Oh! Look at that!
你声音怎么了?怎么突然冒苏格兰口音
What is with your voice? It's all Scottish-y.
哦 好吧 你喜欢不?
Oh! Well, do you like it?
挫透了
It's lame.
- 不喜欢 哟 同志们! 我们遭攻击了
- No. - Yo, peeps! We are under attack!
- 尖叫声在哪里 - 这下好了
- Big whoop. - Fascinating.
他们貌似连危机感都消失了
They seem to be immune to any sense of danger.
哦 真要命 嘿!
Oh for god sakes... Hey!
我们客厅还躺着只死猪呢
We have a dead man-pig in the living room,
我这还有根树枝离不了手
I have a tree stuck to my mitt,
我可不想报名加入幼托俱乐部
and I did not sign up for the babysitter's club!
哦 戴森碰到我的胸了!
Oh, Dyson touched my boob!
这是个意外! 那是我胳膊肘干的!
That was an accident! It was with my elbow!
拜托!这不算!
Doesn't even count! Come on!
不是吧!
Seriously?
同志们 同志们 同志们! 我们点披萨吃吧!
Guys, guys, guys! Let's order pizza!
没错
Yes.
他们三个处于某种原因都被感染了
For some reason, only the 3 of them are infected.
我们要小心点
Let's not take any chances.
不要和他们有肢体接触直到我找到真正病因
No physical contact until I know what we're dealing with.
- 明白了 - 双层奶酪! 好耶!
- Got it. - Double cheese! Yeah!
双层奶酪! 披萨!
Double cheese! PiZZA!
- 披萨! - 披萨!
- Pizza!!! - Pizza!
然后你们三个 乖乖呆着别乱跑
And you three, stay put.
快买披萨来!
Get the pizza!
这些武器你哪儿来的?
Where did you get these??
- 太帕! - 给我一把
- It's fantastic! - Give it to me...
弱爆了
Totally lame...
哇 这还有一把! 你!放马过来吧
Aww... There's another one! Come here, you!
我不明白的是
What I don't understand
要是异种才是感染对象
is that if this disease only targets Fae...
那为什么伐克斯没事呢?
Why isn't Vex infected?
怎么说 也许是我超级逼真的妆容
Well, perhaps my superior genetic makeup
免疫了外界的侵害
has rendered me immune to embarrassing afflictions.
- 那是啥? - 什么?
- What is that? - What?
你耳后有奇怪的脓包
You have a strange pustule behind your ear
我上次给你检查的时候还没有呢
that wasn't there when I examined you last.
脓包 恶
Pustule... Ew.
恶 恶心!
Ugh... Ugh! UGH!
恶心死人了
Ewww with a double side of hurl.
- 这是什么? - 像是什么留下的茧
- What is it?? - It's what's left of a cocoon.
看来你被用作孵卵器了
You've been used as an incubator.
- 被什么当做孵卵器? - 我的猜测
- By what? - My guess?
- 寄生虫 - 什么? 我不干净?
- A parasite. - What? I'm unclean?!
放轻松 已经不在你体内了
Relax... it isn't in you anymore.
但是你哪儿招来的这寄身虫呢?
But where could you have picked this up?
你最近有很陌生异种待一起么?
Have you been with any strange Fae lately?
呃 他妈的贱人!
Ugh... damn bitch!
- 那是怎么了? - 那是怎么了?
- What's that? - What's that?
哦 没事 额
Oh, nothing, uh...
这事搞得我好受伤 额
I was just saying how devastated I was about all this, uh...
听着 我这就去找特里克帮忙 好不?
Listen, I'm gonna get some help from Trick. Alright?
我会想办法补救的 好不?
I'm gonna make things right. Alright?
你他妈对我做了什么?
What the hell did you do to me!?
拿你当传播寄生虫的利器了
Used you to spread a parasite.
- 哪种变态寄生虫 - 吸元寄生的那种
- What kind of bloody parasite!? - The parasitic kind.
靠吸取被害者对他人好感的荷尔蒙为生
Zaps its victims with nymphoid hormones.
把他们变成自恋顽童无法控制异种能力
Turns them into self-obsessed brats too young for Fae powers.
所以 他们易受攻击?
So, they're completely vulnerable to attack?
没错
Precisely.
那那些猪呢? 你派来的?
But what about the "Other white meat"? Relatives of yours?
感染源会发出刺激性荷尔蒙
The infected emit a pungent pheromone that attracts
吸引那些肮脏的下等异种来杀戮
a nasty breed of UnderFae in for the kill.
是啊 幸好肯吉用魔法小木棍把那小猪扭扭
Yeah, well, luckily Kenzi pounded little Piggly Wiggly
揍成了下等异种熏肉
into UnderFae bacon with her magic shillelagh.
- 那个贱女淫妖呢? - 还活蹦乱跳的呢
- And the Succubitch? - Still alive and singing.
还有两个悲剧帝 戴森和他的新搭档
Along with the other Twi-hards. Dyson and his new partner.
哦!事情真是越来越有趣了
Oh! Now this is getting interesting.
我最爱的三个人 被困在了一个地方
Three of my favorite people, trapped in one place...
无法自卫
with no way to defend themselves.
人类小女孩还拿着阿什的魔棒
And she's got The Ash's play stick.
想证明你对黑暗异族的忠诚吗?
You want to prove your loyalty to the Dark?
把那脑残三人组结果了吧
Finish off the teen trio,
然后把正义之杖带回来给我
and bring me the Staff of Righteousness.
要是我做到了?
And if I do?
我可以保证帮你找几个 初级岗位
I'm sure I could find some... entry level position...
做梦! 我要名至实归 百万现金
No! I want all titles restored ... A million in cash
还有我要拿回我的俱乐部
and my club. I want it back.
这才是我认识的伐克斯
There's the Vex I remember.
"赶紧拿个武器"她如是说
"Grab a weapon", she said...
我已经解释好多次了 肯吉 我不知道会这样!
For the hundredth time, Kenzi, I didn't know!
知会媒体同胞 居然有完美医生不知道的事情!
Alert the media, there is something Doctor Flawless doesn't know!
那是紧要关头 肯吉
This is hardly the time, Kenzi.
当然不是 因为要是紧要关头肯定早已一片狼藉
Course it isn't... 'Cause that would be "Messy"!
你不能来一次 一次也行 你能试着
Do you think just once! Maybe just once, you could try to be...
- 试着干嘛? - 有所帮助!
- What? What?? - Helpful!
- 你说什么? - 没错!
- Excuse me? - Sure!
因为大家都尽其所能
Because everybody else does!
你却混混度日 没工作 没计划 成天饮酒作乐
You just bounce through life, no job, no plan, from one beer
每个人都把你捧手心里 难道不是?
to the next and still, everybody dotes on you, don't they?
他们宠谁碍着你什么事了?
What do you care where they dote?
- 当我没说 - 是啊 你这算什么
- Just forget about it... - Yeah... what is that?!
你为什么老用你那正常成长的经历
Why are you always rolling your eyes at me,
和医学学位翻白眼给我看
with your normal upbringing and your medical degree.
我过的是怎样的生活你毫不知情 肯吉
You don't know anything about my life, Kenzi!
我知道你看不起我
I know you think you're too good for me...
不 我真没有 是你觉得我配不上波
No, I don't actually! You think that I'm not good enough for Bo!
- 她是我闺蜜 - 可我也爱她
- She's my best friend. - And I love her.
我知道 我知道
I know! I know.
你确定我们没被感染?
Are you sure we're not infected?
姆
Mmmm...
没 我们只是
No. We're just...
犯傻
...stupid.
好吧 我还是喜欢"情绪化"一词
Well, I prefer... ..."emotional".
不弃前嫌?
Moving on?
- 一起宰猪? - 好
- Killer Pig? - Yeah...
好的
Yep, okay...
我不敢相信我居然以为你不待见我
I can't believe I ever thought you didn't like me.
我不认为我能喜欢你
I don't think I was supposed to like you.
为什么?你这是什么意思?
Why? What do you mean?
我是瓦尔基里
I'm a Valkyrie.
- 好像是 - 哇
- I think. - Wow...
真的?
Really?
- 瓦尔基里是什么? - 我不知道
- What's a Valkyrie? - I don't know.
但是 有时当我有所爱
But... sometimes when I like people,
我却不得不放手
I have to make them go away.
- 你这是什么意思? - 你会保守秘密吗?
- What are you talking about? - Can you keep a secret?
至死不渝
Till I die.
姆
Um...
- 不 我不能说的 - 别 等等 等等!
- No, I'm not supposed to. - No, wait! Wait!
我有个主意 这样
I have an idea! Okay...
我们把自己最黑暗 隐藏最深的秘密以诗的形式
Let's write down our deepest, darkest secrets...
写下来
...in poetry.
酷!
Cool!
但要真的像首诗啊 要押韵的那种
But like real poetry. The kind that rhymes.
你真是个很好的人
You're really awesome.
不 你才是
No. You're really awesome.
额
Um...
哦 哦!
Oh, oh!
看到那猪脸了吗?
See its snout?
它的遗传结构与猪相似
It's similar in genetic makeup to the pig.
他以气味捕食猎物 他知道我们之中
It was scenting out its prey, it knew which of us
谁感染了寄生虫
was infected with the parasite.
块菌猪威武霸气
Hurray for the Truffle Pig.
这种生物群居为生
These creatures travel in packs.
当他们的兄弟没有回去
When their buddy doesn't return...
他们就群攻?
They'll all go hog wild?
我们的魔法棒也不够救咱们的
Not even my wonder whacker may be enough to save us.
所以我们需要波和其他人恢复正常
That's why we need Bo and the others back to normal.
根据我从伐克斯耳后的茧中提取的分泌物
Based on the secretions that I pulled from the cocoon
我可以凑出个寄生虫的抗生素
from Vex, I think I can cobble together an anti-toxin
- 但我需要时间 - 也许还要个实验室
- for the parasite. But I need time. - And a lab, maybe?
好吧 这倒不必 我工具箱里有些基本配备
Well, not necessarily. I've got a few basic supplies in my kit.
但我需要你帮我去凑齐几味配料
But I need you to gather up some ingredients.
呃 发酵粉 醋 姜黄
Uh, baking powder, vinegar, turmeric...
好 好 好的
Yeah, yeah, okay...
好了 说吧
Alright, go...
还有 大蒜 发胶和润滑油
Also, garlic, hairspray, and lubricating oil.
加工的还是散装的?
Flavoured or bulk?
至于我 我要去楼上采样
As for me... I'm going upstairs to take a swab.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
医生 你单枪匹马的去了? 不带个后援?
Doc, you goin' in solo? Without backup?
- 我能搞定 - 你的固执和专横真是半斤八两
- I think I can do this. - You're as stubborn as you are bossy.
祝你成功
Godspeed.
好吧!
Okay!
- 发生什么事了? - 不想说这个
- What happened? - I don't want to talk about it.
但是 我拿到样本了
But... I got it.
的确
Sure did.
哇
Wow...
- 做的不错 - 是啊 我还会干其他事
- Nice job. - Yeah, I did something else too...
我还在外面装了一个预警系统 小鬼当家范儿
I set up an early warning system outside, Home Alone style.
很好 会有帮助的
Good. That'll help.
好了
Okay...
你肯定毕业于哪个疯人医学院
You must've gone to some crazy-ass medical school.
耶鲁教会了我化学和生理学
Yale taught me chemistry and physiology.
但是这东西只是经验和运气
But this kind of stuff is just experience and luck
是我实地经验琢磨出来的
and whatever I figured out in the field.
- 实地说的是 - 阿富汗
- "Field" Meaning... - Afghanistan.
要命 姐们
Shit, dude...
- 呆了多长时间 - 长到都忘记了
- How long? - Long enough.
- 你以前怎么不曾提起? - 你又没问
- Why didn't you ever say so? - You never asked.
你在听戴森尿尿
You're listening to Dyson take a whiz.
我才没有
I am not.
你读了我的诗没? 写的很烂 是吧?
Did you read my poem? It was stupid, right?
没 我喜欢 很喜欢
No, I liked it. A lot.
在某种程度上 你写的很美
Yours was really beautiful... in a way.
但是这故事真的 真的很悲伤
But it was... really, really sad.
我真希望能做些什么可以帮到你
I wish there was something I could do to help you.
你帮不了我的
You can't help me.
没人帮得了我
Nobody can.
这是我们的秘密?
Our secret?
我发誓
Cross my heart.
请把我变成异妖吧
Make mine a Fae-cuccino, please...
我刚刚过滤了杂质 老天 我希望
I'm just straining any impurities. God, I hope...
警报响起!
Perimeter breach!
- 额 我们有伴了 - 有多少?
- Uh... we've got company! - How many?
只有 额 不是 还有一个
There's just... Uh, no, there's another one...
- 呃 药还没做好 - 哦 老天
- Ugh, it's not ready! - Oh, God...
三头小猪驾到! 这回可是人为哦
The 3 little piggies are back! And this time, it's personal.
- 伐克斯! 老兄 你这是在干嘛?
- Vex! - Dude, what are you doing?
我要回家了
I'm going home.
- 你这虚伪的混蛋 - 噢
- You slimy sonuvabitch! - Ooooh!
这话真是伤我心啊!
Your words are like tiny little daggers in my heart!
我那么相信你!
I trusted you!
那么 把淘气小淫妖交出来 让我们早点打道回府!
Yeah, well, just give us the rugrats so we can all go home!
休想!
Not on your miserable life!
杜兰杜兰乐队的歌?
Duran Duran?
波!救命!
Bo! Help!
好像是肯吉在叫你诶!
That sounds like Kenzi!
我饥饿如狼
"...I'm hungry like the wolf!"
波?!
Bo?!
- 把声音调大点 塔米! - 好
- Crank it, Tammy! - Okay!
解毒剂准备完毕!
The antidote's ready!
- 我得上楼一趟 - 有多远跑多远 医生!
- I need to get upstairs... - Go long and wide, Doc!
我掩护你!
I got you covered!
你没事吗?
Are you gonna be okay??
当然! 还挺有趣
Sure! This is kinda fun.
好吧 我设法别胡思乱想
Okay... Way to not overthink it.
嗨 小闪妞
Hey... Twinkle toes...
你的权杖我也要了
I'll be havin' that wee Staff of yours.
靠近点 我递给你
Come closer. Let me give it you.
哦 我太高兴了 看看我找到了什么
Oh, I'd be delighted. Look what I found.
这和我以前
This isn't really like...
玩过的转瓶游戏大不一样啊
any Spin The Bottle game I ever played.
- 哦 规则更新了 - 你确定?
- Oh, it's new rules. - Are you sure?
确定 我不知在哪儿 看过 轮到你了
Absolutely, I read it... somewhere. It's your turn.
- 我得吻你 - 好吧
- I gotta kiss you. - Okay.
- 天 你到底是谁? - 姐们 那是你的关系
- Man... what are you? - Dude... that was all you.
你们这是在玩转瓶游戏?
Are you playing Spin The Bottle?
爽毙了
That was so dope.
- 我们再来 - 好的
- Let's do that again. - Okay.
好吧 还是别了
Yeah, let's not...
喔
Ow!!!
- 嘿 我们的披萨呢? - 不会有披萨了
- Hey, where's our pizza? - There's no pizza coming.
过来啊 你个小
Come here, you little...
啊哈
Ahh...
我觉得你要说的应该是傻瓜一词
I believe "Wanker" Is the word that you're looking for.
你个卑鄙的叛徒
A dirty traitor!
想想我还和你共享了
And to think I shared my
我的限量版紫精灵闪粉
limited edition purple-pixie glitter with you!
哇 你以为共享化妆品就让我们成朋友了?
Aw, you think sharing makeup makes us friends?
别这样 你能自己做主
Don't do this... I thought you were your own man.
我的确是自己的主宰啊 而且我刚好有把斧头
I am my own man! And I happen to have an axe.
但是你不是为了自己才干这事的
But you're not doing this for you.
你这么做是为了那个贱女人
You're doing it for that stupid bitch!
做什么也比这有格调
Anything is better than this!
我是说 看看我! 我睡沙发!
I mean, look at me! I'm sleeping on a couch!
人们都当面嘲笑我!
People are laughing at me to my face!
你不能相信莫瑞根
You can't believe that The Morrigan's
她不会满心欢喜的欢迎你
just gonna welcome you back with open arms!
听着 亲爱的 明显你也看过那本
Listen, luv, you've obviously read the book
人质谈判第一章第一篇 所以我们能跳页么
on "Hostage Negotiation 101"... Can we just skip
说说我活成这样哪里好了
to the bit where you tell me I'm better than this?
- 这样的你好 - 要是不好呢
- You are. - What if I'm not?
你失去了异种能力
Losing your powers was the
对你来说是最好的事情
best thing that could have happened to you.
我感觉我终于看到了真正的伐克斯
I feel like I've finally met the real Vex!
他是真正的艺术家! 他温文尔雅!
He's a true artist. He's a gentle soul!
而且他不会被轻易愚弄 莫瑞根也不行
And he will not be trifled with. Not even by her!
他已经受够了
He's done with that!
伐克斯 拜托!
Vex... please!
哦 肯吉
Oh, Kenzi...
我在年迈之时变温柔了
I'm getting soft in my old age.
明智的选择
Good choice...
Good choice!!!
没事了
It's all right...
她来了
She's coming...
是时候老娘虐猪做熏肉了
Time for Mama to bring home the bacon.
- 哦 - 哦!
- Oh... - Oh!
我觉得被美人揍
I don't think I'd mind getting my ass kicked
- 我一定也不介意 - 可是很疼的
- by someone that hot. - That had to hurt.
恶
Ugh...
- 啊哈! - 哦 老天!
- Ah! - Oh! God!
还有一个 还有一个 还有一个!
One to go, one to go, one one one to go!
还有两个 不 那有两个!
And that's two! No, that's two!
波最棒!
Bo for the gold!
呃 结局皆大欢喜 是吧?
Ahem... Uh, all's well that ends well, yeah?
无恶意?
No hard feelings?
喔
Ow!
妞 你还真有一手 真话
Girl, you got you some gaaame. True.
加油 波
Come on, Bo...
发生了啥事 完全不记得了
The whole thing's... blank.
头晕晕的 就像
But fuzzy, like...
的确发生了什么 但是不记得了?
...like there's something there, but why can't I remember?
因为你本该忘记
Because you're not supposed to.
我们还是别纠结的好
We're probably better off this way.
是啊 注意不错 塔米
Yeah, good call, Tammy.
- 我是说 塔米辛 - 好吧
- I mean, Tamsin. - Okay!
听着 我就知道最近这破事
Look, all I know is that this latest crapfest
害我又多了几份异种报告要写
just caused a whole mess of Fae paperwork.
所以 谢谢你毁了我的周末 还有再见
So, thank you for destroying my weekend, and goodbye.
好吧 这姑娘一点都不幽默
Well, that girl is just no fun at all.
姆
Hmm...
执正义之杖之人
The one who touches the Staff of Righteousness
必须行使高尚之举
shall take up the noble cause,
接受山林仙子宁芙的神圣斗篷
accept the sacred mantle of Ruler of Forest Nymphs
继承丛林精神 发誓至始至终
and Wood Sprites, and fight for truth and justice
只为正义和真理而战
throughout the land to the end of their natural days.
这是在玩我吧
You're kidding me.
你继承了一个重大的责任
This is a huge responsibility you've taken on.
我就是信手拈来了个棍子!
I just picked up a frikkin' stick!
这就是传说中命运 今天你还是你 明天
That's how destiny works. One day you're you, and the next day...
我就成了超级英雄
I'm a superhero.
好处
Pro...
我看起来永远很
I could be awesome, forever.
- 没错 - 好吧 坏处
- Yup. - Okay... Con...
我得开始学习惯用左手
I would have to learn how to do everything
我是说干啥都得左手
with my left hand and I mean everything.
好吧 作为最后 有个免除条款
Well... as a last, desperate resort there is an escape clause.
选了 赶紧告诉我怎么脱离这棍子
Sold. Show me the eject button.
好吧
Very well.
闭上眼然后跟我念 不准偷瞄
Close your eyes and say the words... No peeking.
我拒绝
"I decline".
我 拒绝
I... decline.
就这么简单?
It was that easy?
你怎么不早说?
Why didn't you just say so?
干嘛? 血圣就不能找乐子么?
What? A Blood King can't have a little fun?
你的室内装潢师水平真不咋地
I don't think much of your interior decorator...
这只是还在装修中
It's a work in progress.
和你一样
Much like yourself.
别转移话题 这事还没完
Don't change the subject. You're not off the hook yet.
哦 看看你 瞬间老成相的阿什
Oh! Look at you. All grown up. "The Ash."
你有印新商务名片么
Did you get the new business cards,
也许买了车办了自选车牌
yet? Maybe a little vanity plate?
- 当爹的好光荣 - 你违反了异种法律
- Daddy must be so proud. - You violated Fae law.
哦 就逗逗淫妖这点小事么?
Oh, by having a little fun with SuccuBo?
你招摇过市攻击光明异族
You executed a blatant attack on the Light.
哦 拜托 啥时候大家都这么神经过敏了?
Oh, come on now. When did everyone get so uptight?
我仍记得当年
I remember the good old days.
小抢小闹
A little raping, a little pillaging,
古怪的"附带损坏"
the odd "Collateral damage"...
然后再给自己办个派对
and then you'd have yourself a party.
现在干嘛都是规则 规则
Now it's all rules, rules, rules.
你的行为会破坏新的和平计划
Your actions may have jeopardized the new peace plan.
怕你忘记 提醒你一下 这计划
A plan, in case you've forgotten,
是由异种长老们决议通过的
that was endorsed by the Fae Elders themselves.
我能说什么?
What can I say?
除了 我错了
Except, mea culpa.
我就是想为生活添点情趣
I was just trying to spice things up a little bit.
我做了三十年的警察了
I was a cop for thirty years.
学会一件事 屁话臭不可闻
One thing I learned... bullshit stinks.
女士 你臭气熏天了
And lady, you reek.
你要是再敢耍花招
You ever pull a stunt like this again,
我会亲自宰了你
I will personally rip off
让你好看
your head and shove it up your lily white ass.
这次紧张局面缓和相当重要
This détente is important to be screwed up
不能被琐碎的小争执给破坏了
by some petty feud.
听清楚了没?
Am I clear?
明白了
Crystal.
嗨 兄弟 我们刚从伐克斯缺席的嘉年华上回来
Hey man, we are just one Vex short of a real fiesta.
你要去哪儿?
Where you goin'?
还不知道
I don't know yet.
我去泡点茶
Why don't I go make some tea.
伐克斯亲 嗨 拜托 我们都不计前嫌了
Vexster... hey! Come on, all is forgiven.
不能 肯吉
But it shouldn't be, Kenz.
我不能住这儿了 在我做了这样的事之后
I can't stay here. Not after what I've done.
老兄 你救了我的命
Dude, you saved my life...
那只是那猪刚好移到了左边
Or that pig shifted to the left at just the right moment.
才不是
That is not true.
不是 对吧
Is it??
你懂得
You know...
如果我翻过我的历史 你就会知道我是个赌徒
if you'd looked at my history you'd know I was a betting man.
我要花点时间自舔伤口 你知道吗?
I'm going to take some time to reflect, you know?
重启系统 我猜医生说得对!
Reset the system. I guess the Doctor was right!
见鬼的人类
Bloody humans...
- 你这是要去西藏? - 印度 路经维加斯
- You thinkin' maybe Tibet? - India, via Vegas.
你懂得 整个美食 祈祷 催眠之旅
You know, the whole Eat, Pray, Mesmer tour.
是啊 我会回来的
Yeah... well... I'll be back.
全副武装 准备就绪
Fully armed and ready to rock.
那我什么时候才能再见你?
How do I know I'll ever see you again?
不会是你黑檀木手柄猪鬃胭脂刷吧?
Not your ebony handled bison bristle blush brush?
呃
Ugh!
你要是搞坏了 我非杀了你不可
You break that brush and I'll kill ya.
嗷
Ow!
来世再见 也许
Catch you in another lifetime! Maybe...
我会想念那混蛋的
I'm gonna miss that a-hole...
我知道
I know.
- 噢 - 来吃
- Ow... - Here...